Thank you so much for this evening and for the gift of life you've given us.
I thank you for each person in this room and the responsibility that's in the hands of our
council. I pray that you give them wisdom and give them compassion and I pray that as we,
as a citizens of this city, take responsibility for our own actions, where I pray that we
would do are very best to honor you and everything we do and say. We are grateful for the
freedoms that we've been given and we celebrate those things here today. We ask all this in
Jesus' name.
Thank you, Lordy, on TV at June 9.
You're being non-identivising in the Senate agenda. Staff is recommending item 6 through 9 for the
consent agenda. There are no questions on it. Those items that are being motion to approve.
Most people may.
And second. Second.
Go call them O'S.
Johnson.
All right.
Western.
So.
I, on.
I, on tier world and financial services to update the late study report, Tyler.
Yes, sir. I'm Tony and Jackson. I will end. He has requested an additional $1,500 to update the
late study for the date changes as far as how we change. The electric rate to start June this
year and then able every subsequent year and then also to change it to the January for
our answer if we do go ahead and approve that. So that way we can see their expected revenues
that will be taken in in that time for budget for bonding.
Anything.
Indeed, is that something you think it's necessary that we have to do just because of the bonding
issue that we need to have an experts.
I definitely do because that is what Greg Nito or anybody else that does our bonds is going
to be basing that on.
Okay.
So I think it's money well spent when you consider the amount of money we're talking about borrowing.
Any other questions on that issue?
Do we have a motion to approve?
I like the motion.
I'll start.
Go, please.
Rest in.
Johnson.
So.
Hi.
Adam 11 is a world good C-1784 A to Tri-State Trucks Center for Refuge Truck and Approach Contract
contingent upon submission of all required contract documents.
Yes sir.
So this is Kevin Horn and myself.
We received three beds for this.
Two of the beds came from Tri-State Trucks Center and the third bed came from Summit.
First bed that we received from Tri-State.
It did not include the warranties that we requested in the big documents for the body.
and for the truck so we are asking tonight to go with their second bid, which include the
warranties as we requested and they were still the lowest at $362,636 in 40 cents.
Okay, what kind of truck is this? I know what says where if you truck, but this is a back
to big pig truck. It's a front load. It dumps over the front end. It's for the commercial.
Yes, okay. I remember talking about that now. I did think they talked about another.
So how long will it be before we're going to be required to make the changes to the dumpsters
for that truck to work?
We've asked that they'd be done by January of 2018.
No, July of 2018.
And a lot of people are already doing it. We've done a lot of occasions to commercial customers.
We've chosen, I know that I had the email and presented and they chose to wait just a little
long. I think we're going to go with brand new dumpsters instead of the retrofit.
I mean, it just makes sense.
But this warranty here is that a factory implied warranty that it's an extended warranty.
It looks like a big warranty is on both of them, but it's only like a one year factory warranty.
This gives us like a five year warranty here.
Okay.
I really glad that can also be used to raise the bench also.
Yes, there is a box on the front, a carry can on the front that can be used as residential.
When you do the commercial can, you have to take that off.
But it's just two hydraulic connections and a couple of safety.
Yes.
There's one other thing I think is important to talk about in acquiring this.
This is hardware for us.
Getting in, but this can be operated by one person instead of three.
As we currently have, and our plans are that the two FTEs that are assigned to this would be assigned to the water department and the street department.
Both of those departments, there's been a need for additional personnel to be able to do a lot of routine maintenance.
So that's been a long-term plan.
If that's a plan we'll put together when we put together our current year budget,
but it takes us amount of time to acquire a piece of equipment like that, but that's still the plan.
And that way we increase the number of people we have assigned to streets and water, but we do not increase our FTE account.
I'm kind of concerned about our place because we've got 480 coming in above head and I can't see how they're going to come in.
We've got a gate around where the dumpsters are at.
Somebody got to open a gate for you.
And then they have to come in at a different direction, I guess.
We'll just have to work with you all to be able to do it.
But you'll have to have access and then they run.
You don't have to clear it.
Not all the time.
I don't know what the overhead plan says.
We'll be able to say 480.
You don't want to come to contact with them.
Okay.
Any other questions or comments?
So we have a motion to approve of the revised bid.
You do.
Motion to approve.
Yeah, that's all second to all.
So a couple of please.
Johnson.
I.
You business and a new business.
They need a new business.
No, you're on it.
I have a fortune in your pocket.
I need a trusted community announcement.
Okay.
I don't.
15 is a German.
I have motion to approve.
First adjourn.
Second.